<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_title">Barbie</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle"><b>Barbie doll: Description</b></string>
    <string name="article_text">Barbie is a fashion doll manufactured by the American
        toy company Mattel, Inc. and launched in March 1959. American businesswoman Ruth Handler is credited
        with the creation of the doll using a German doll called Bild Lilli as her inspiration.
        Barbie is the figurehead of a brand of Mattel dolls and accessories, including other family members and collectible
        dolls. \n\nBarbie has been an important part of the toy fashion doll market for over sixty years, and has been the subject
        of numerous controversies and lawsuits, often involving parodies of the doll and her lifestyle. Mattel has sold over a
        billion Barbie dolls, making it the company largest and most profitable line.\n\n

<b><i>History</i></b> - Ruth Handler watched her daughter Barbara play with paper dolls, and noticed that she often enjoyed giving
        them adult roles. At the time, most children toy dolls were representations of infants. Realizing that there could be a
        gap in the market, Handler suggested the idea of an adult-bodied doll to her husband Elliot, a co-founder of the Mattel
        toy company. He was unenthusiastic about the idea, as were Mattel directors.\n\n
        During a trip to Europe in 1956 with her children Barbara and Kenneth, Ruth Handler came across a German toy doll called
        Bild Lilli. The adult-figured doll was exactly what Handler had in mind, so she purchased three of them. She gave one to
        her daughter and took the others back to Mattel. The Lilli doll was based on a popular character appearing in a comic
        strip drawn by Reinhard Beuthin for the newspaper Bild. Lilli was a blonde bombshell, a working girl who knew what
        she wanted and was not above using men to get it. The Lilli doll was first sold in Germany in 1955, and although it
        was initially sold to adults, it became popular with children who enjoyed dressing her up in outfits that were available separately.

                \n\n
<b><i>Fictional Biography</i></b>  —  Barbies full name is Barbara Millicent Roberts. In a series of novels published by Random House in the 1960s,
        her parents names are given as George and Margaret Roberts from the fictional town of Willows, Wisconsin. In the Random
        House novels, Barbie attended Willows High School; while in the Generation Girl books, published by Golden Books in 1999,
        she attended the fictional Manhattan International High School in New York City (based on the real-life Stuyvesant High
        School).

</string>
</resources>
