<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TwoActivitiesChallange</string>
    <string name="button1">Button1</string>
    <string name="button2">Button2</string>
    <string name="button3">Button3</string>

    <string name="displayText_one">Avatar the Last Airbender:  The world is divided into four nations -- the Water Tribe, the Earth Kingdom,
        the Fire Nation and and the Air Nomads -each represented by a natural element for which the nation is named.
        Benders have the ability to control and manipulate the element from their nation. Only the Avatar is the master of all four elements.
        The ruthless Fire Nation wants to conquer the world but the only bender who has enough power, the Avatar, has disappeared ...
        until now. His tribe soon discovers that Aang is the long-lost Avatar. Now Katara and Sokka must safeguard Aang on his journey to master
        all four elements and save the world from the Fire Nation</string>

    <string name="displayText_two">One Piece: a Japanese manga series written and illustrated by Eiichiro Oda.
        It has been serialized in Shueishas shonen manga magazine Weekly Shōnen Jump since July 1997, with its individual chapters
        compiled into 102 tankobon volumes as of April 2022. The story follows the adventures of Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body gained
        the properties of rubber after unintentionally eating a Devil Fruit. With his pirate crew, the Straw Hat Pirates, Luffy explores
        the Grand Line in search of the world ultimate treasure known as the "One Piece" in order to become the next King of the Pirates.
        The manga spawned a media franchise, having been adapted into a festival film produced by Production I.G, and an anime series produced by
        Toei Animation, which began broadcasting in Japan in 1999. Additionally, Toei has developed fourteen animated feature films, one OVA
        and thirteen television specials. Several companies have developed various types of merchandising and media, such as a trading card game
        and numerous video games. The manga series was licensed for an English language release in North America and the United Kingdom by Viz
        Media and in Australia by Madman Entertainment.</string>

    <string name="displayText_three">One-Punch Man a Japanese superhero franchise created by the artist ONE. It tells the story of Saitama,
        a superhero who can defeat any opponent with a single punch but seeks to find a worthy opponent after growing bored by a lack of
        challenge due to his overwhelming strength. ONE wrote the original webcomic version in early 2009.
        A digital manga remake began publication on Shueishas Tonari no Young Jump website in June 2012. The manga is illustrated by
        Yusuke Murata, and its chapters are periodically compiled and published into individual tankōbon volumes. As of December 2021,
        24 volumes have been released. In North America, Viz Media has licensed the remake manga for English language release and was
        serialized in its Weekly Shonen Jump digital magazine.</string>
</resources>